MEGAN REED —www.meganreed.com —reed.megan.n@gmail.com

Designer of experiences & digital products. Advocate of the user. Into hospitality/travel tech at the intersection of high-tech & high-touch. Successfully builds products collaborating with dev & product teams around the world. Hits the ground running across the full spectrum of UX/product design—has a holistic view of entire product flow and dabbles in code to bring wireframes and visual designs to life.

Recent Experience

UX Design Lead New York City 2019-Current

Leading user experience design for **Avero**, an international hospitality management software company providing operators with reporting & solutions based on data insights.

Manages design execution and delivery with ownership of all aspects of product design, including UX/UI program and resource development.

Established process to collaborate with product & engineering to reduce development costs and time; cutting speed to market in half while significantly increasing quality of design deliverables.

Reduced support costs and customer complaints through using data and user research to design a more usable UI; achieving increased adoption and 92% customer renewal rate.

Digital Product Designer Miami 2015-19

Brought on to drive product design efforts and scale services for hospitality startup, **EveryBell**, built to bring luxury hotel-style services to residences and rentals.

Designed & developed website and mobile app as a platform for service execution and mobile bookings; achieved recognition in 2015 & 2016 Best of Miami Business (Hospitality-Small Business).

Delivered end-to-end user experience solutions for multiple highimpact projects focused on hospitality & travel tech; presenting design assets to Managing Director and Senior Design Leader.

Senior Manager, Marketing & Product Singapore 2013-15

At **Stamford**, managed a local team of 10+ and collaborated with remote team of 6, including designers & engineers; achieving aggressive business growth of 600% year-over-year.

Directed complete product design cycle to launch new web portal that caused user engagement and retention to shoot up 165%.

Creative direction from concept-to-execution on all marketing and digital products while responsible for \$1M budget; including marketing plan & campaign strategy, high-profile event execution, digital & print advertising, partnership negotiations, video & editorial content creation, etc.

Education & Skills

Primary Tools Figma, Sketch, Adobe CC, InVision, HTML, CSS, GitHub (open to and experienced in using others)

Focus Areas UX Ideation & Strategy, DesignOps & process management, user research, rapid wireframes & prototypes, visual UI mockups

UX/UI Design & Front-End Development Bloc.io 2016-17 B.S. Business Administration, Marketing CCU 2002-06

Further Design Education Specialized courses, workshops, events focused on design systems & process, UX writing, entrepreneurship, AI, voice interaction design

Highlighted Projects

Hotelify Web UX design and front-end development of website, UX strategy for back-end management web appused to scale guest services & communication for independent hotels.

UpStay Mobile Led concept-to-production product design cycle for mobile on-demand bookings. Followed lean startup, highly-iterative process with user data and insights informing design decisions.

SommMe Chatbot Interaction UX strategy & design for concept prototype of wine pairing app. Also owned product brand identity, user research, UI design.

Past Experience

Marketing & Guest Experience 2006-13 USA, Singapore

Began at **Intuit**, responsible for regional territory merchandising for small business solutions and tax deduction software products in retail locations.

Drove guest experience initiatives while managing creative direction, menu design, PR & event planning at Four Seasons Hotels & Resorts. Awarded collaborative responsibility on a \$1M re-design project for new restaurant concept becoming the #1 Fine Dining Restaurant in Hawaii.

Collaborated with product/sales/marketing teams at HRS

The Hotel Portal to grow into APAC market and increase user onboarding success for B2B portal; driving bookings up by 40% with pipeline of \$2M per campaign.